Guide to the Horticultural Society of New York Records 1811-circa 2010 (bulk, 1900-circa 2010) MS 3033
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Photographs, 1917-2006; 22.73 Linear feet
  - Subseries V.E. Other Images, 1917, 1940s-2002 (bulk, 1950s-1970s); 17.82 Linear feet
    Although much of the subseries has a certain degree of randomness to it and ambiguity as to context, several portions are well-defined and substantive. These include a captioned photograph album of World War I scenes of troop movements and trench warfare with their related destruction of trees in France (1917); lantern slides of Mrs. Louis Levy's azalea and rock garden in Dobbs Ferry, NY; a photograph album documenting a trip to Japan (1967); sets of educational slides concerning sowing and repotting and turfgrass diseases; images by recognized photographers Ralph Bailey of House & Garden and Bruce Cratsley; an organized set of slides depicting seasonal wildflowers; and two photograph albums of cacti cultivated by Richard Weiler.
    There was no overall original order to the images in this subseries. They were compiled together and arranged by the processing archivist. Nonetheless, images found together in slide cases, sleeves, folders, etc., were kept together as found. The overall subseries is arranged roughly in the following sequence, though there is considerable overlap at points:
    1) Images emphasizing places or travel, including gardens and grounds
    2) Images emphasizing the work of a particular photographer or of a particular subject
    3) Images emphasizing particular plants or types of plants.
    - Places: Greece, Corsica and Other Europe; Caribbean, Central and South America; Middle East and Africa. (Slides) (4 folders), 1960s-1981 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4-7)
    - Places: Italy (Slides) (3 cases), 1960s (Offsite-box 6, Slide-case 1-3)
    - Places: Japan Travel Photo Album, 1967 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    - Places: Tucson (transparencies) (2 folders), undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9-10)
    - Places: Rooftop Garden, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
    - Places: Scott Appel's Florida Trip, 2002 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
    - Places: Washington Cathedral Grounds (Photos by Bonde & Sons), undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
    - Places: Mrs. Louis S. Levy's Azalea and Rock Garden, Dobbs Ferry, NY. Glass Lantern Slides #1-72 (1 of 2 boxes), undated (Box 11, Item 1-72)
      Includes a descriptive key to the slides in this box and the next, prepared in 2008.
    - Places: Mrs. Louis S. Levy's Azalea and Rock Garden, Dobbs Ferry, NY. Glass Lantern Slides #73-91 (2 of 2 boxes), undated (Box 12, Item 1-19)
    - Places: Mrs. Louis S. Levy's Azalea and Rock Garden, Dobbs Ferry, NY. Glass Lantern Slides. Extras, Sections 1-8 (1 of 2 boxes), undated (Box 12, Item -)
      Includes a descriptive key to the additional Levy slides found in this box and the next.
    - Places: Mrs. Louis S. Levy's Azalea and Rock Garden, Dobbs Ferry, NY. Glass Lantern Slides. Extras, Sections 9-15 (2 of 2 boxes), undated (Box 13, Item -)
    - Places: Europe, United States, Other. (Slides) (21 cases in flat box), 1950s-1970s (Offsite-box 106, Box FF-2, Slide-case 1-21)
      Includes 21 small boxes of 35mm slides, mostly of Europe, but also many of the eastern U.S. Many are also of unidentified locations.
    - Places: Italy/Austria, Miscellaneous (Negatives), 1962 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
      Tentatively identified as the Netherlands, Japan, and the southern U.S.
    - Places: Unidentified Tours, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
    - Places: Miscellaneous Prints, undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
      Includes Mohonk Mountain House, Trinity Church (Manhattan) graveyard, Old Westbury Gardens, Frelinghuysen arboretum, Stamford arboretum & nature center, and private gardens.
    - Places: Miscellaneous Slides, 1960s-1980s (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17)
    - Places: Wilton Gardens (2 folders), 1979 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 18-19)
    - Places: Port Washington?, 1970s (Offsite-box 77, Folder 20)
    - Photographer: Ralph Bailey. Correspondence, 1960, 1968 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 18)
    - Photographer: Ralph Bailey. Photographs (6 folders), undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 19-24)
    - Photographer: Ralph Bailey. Duke Foundation Gardens (Negatives), undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 25)
    - Photographer: Ralph Bailey. (Slides in Flat Box), undated (Offsite-box 106, Box FF-2, Slide-case 1)
    - Photographer: Bruce Cratsley. Photographs. (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Lincoln Center's Henry Moore Sculpture Pool and Beaumont Theatre.
    - Photographer: Bruce Cratsley. Photographs. (2 of 2). (Flat Box), 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 6)
    - Photographer: Peter Fink (Flat Box), undated (Offsite-box 107, Folder 5)
    - Photographer: Chris Phinney (Flat Box), undated (Offsite-box 108, Folder 3)
    - Photographer: Ellen Stockdale-Wolfe (Flat Box), 2003 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 4)
      Includes the color photograph Purple Loose Strife, Millbrook, NY, print 1/50, in memory of Eleanor Lamanna Stockdale.
    - Photographer: John Yang (Flat Box), 1982 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 4)
      Includes one photograph of the garden of Schneider and Parnas in Wilton, CT, inscribed to Luther Greene from Yang (negative #326-11, 5/11/82).
    - Subjects: WWI Scenes in France (Flat Box), 1917 (Offsite-box 105, Box FF-1, Item 1)
      Includes a photo album with images from France in World War I. Includes photos of troops, troop movements, and troops in trenches. A focus of many of the photos is the destruction of fruit and other trees. The photos are captioned in French. The pages are fragile. Separate sheets include captions in English and background documents.
    - Subjects: Bird Houses (Transparencies), undated (Offsite-box 4, Folder 27)
    - Subjects: Jimmy Carter, Peanut Farmer, 1968 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 28)
      Includes one photograph of future U.S. President Jimmy Carter holding some of a peanut crop in Plains, Georgia.
    - Subjects: Clarence L. Hay, circa 1970 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 29)
      Includes the unframed photograph and related label from the HSNY room named in memory of Hay (1884-1969).
    - Subjects: Various Slides (2 folders), 1960s-1970s (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1-2)
      Includes miscellaneous slides depicting gardening, types of gardens, plants in a garden setting (e.g., shrubs, vines, lawns, topiaries, etc.), decorative fixtures, and the like.
    - Subjects: Sowing, Pricking Out & Repotting (Slides in Flat Box), undated (Offsite-box 106, Slide-case 1)
      Includes a set of slides for an educational program by J.S. Dakers.
    - Subjects: Diseases of Turfgrass (Slides in Flat Box), undated (Offsite-box 106, Slide-case 1)
      Includes a set of slides for an educational program compiled by the New York State Turfgrass Association, by R.W. Smiley of Cornell.
    - Subjects: Trelease Selenium Lecture, 1940s? (Offsite-box 7, Slide-case 6)
      Includes a case with a set of slides that appears to be a lecture on selenium content of plants (black-taped slides). Also in the case are other slides that may or may not be related. Some of these slides are of plants and rocks seen on a trip in the western U.S. Other slides are of miscellaneous plants.
    - Subjects: Zoo Animals (Slides in Flat Box), undated (Offsite-box 106, Slide-case 1)
    - Plants: Richard Weiler Photograph Albums of Cacti (2 folders), 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3-4)
      Includes photographs of the cacti as displayed in the solarium of the New York Athletic Club.
    - Plants: Cannabis (Transparencies), undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
    - Plants: Plant Propagation, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
    - Plants: Carnivorous, 1974 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - Plants: Ferns, Lichens, Manuscript Images (Slides), 1960s-1970s (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - Plants: Flower Arrangements, 1935-1951 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - Plants: Flower Arrangements (from albums), 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - Plants: Flower Arrangements, 1967 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
    - Plants: Flower Arrangements, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 12)
    - Plants: Tulipieres from Tulipomania, 1979 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 13)
    - Plants: Wildflowers Slides, 1986 (Offsite-box 10, Slide-case 1-3)
      Includes three sets of slides of wildflowers, labelled, organized and donated to HSNY by Robert York.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Gardens & Arrangements, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 14)
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Photographic Prints (4 of 6 folders), undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 15-18)
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Photographic Prints (2 of 6 folders), 1930s-1980s (Offsite-box 77, Folder 21-22)
      Includes a photograph of an olive grove by Jesse Tarbox Beals (used on the cover of a Bulletin in 1937), various flower arrangements that won prizes in the 1930s, Mayor Edward Koch with tulips at City Hall Park, and spring garden pilgrimage in 1938.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Transparencies, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 19)
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Negatives, undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 20)
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Slides (1 of 3 boxes), 1940s, undated (Offsite-box 7, Slide-case 1-6)
      This box and the next two include various sets of 35mm slides concerning various plants. Most of the slides are undated, but those that are dated are from 1940-43. Most of the slides are unidentified. Those with identification are of plants, with identification as to where the photo was taken. These locations are generally New Jersey (e.g., Brielle, Matawan) and New York City parks or the greater metropolitan area. The sets are numbered from 1-55, 106-109, and 121-139; each individual slide is marked as part of a particular set.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Slides (2 of 3 boxes), 1940s, undated (Offsite-box 8, Slide-case 1-5)
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Slides (3 of 3 boxes), 1940s, undated (Offsite-box 9, Slide-case 1-4)
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Slides, 1960s-1990s (Offsite-box 106, Box FF-3, Slide-case 1-35)
      Includes one flat box with several small cases, boxes, and envelopes of 35mm slides.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Lantern Slides (1 of 4 boxes), undated (Box 25, Item 1-48)
      Includes a set of 24 slides produced by J. Horace McFarland Company of Harrisburg, Pennsylvania; a set of 11 slides depicting gardens with Tudor-style houses; and 13 slides of men working in gardens.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Lantern Slides (2 of 4 boxes), undated (Box 26, Item 1-47)
      Includes 47 slides of gardens and houses.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Lantern Slides (3 of 4 boxes), undated (Box 27, Item 1-53)
      Includes 53 slides of plants, gardens, redwood forests, and other similar, varied images. These continue into the next box. Some slides are negatives.
    - Plants: Miscellaneous Lantern Slides (4 of 4 boxes), undated (Box 28, Item 1-67)
- Series VI. Print Matter, 1811-circa 2010; 22.19 Linear feet
  Series VI. Print Matter, 1811-circa 2010 is divided into the following subseries:
  Subseries VI.A. Hort Periodicals, 1900-1998
  Subseries VI.B. Other Hort Print Matter, 1901-circa 2010
  Subseries VI.C. Miscellaneous Print Material, 1811-1997
  The Print Matter series includes a broad range of printed materials, including Hort periodicals, books or booklets published by the Hort, program calendars, and ephemera. The materials span the Hort's founding in 1900 to the early twenty-first century. The periodicals range from 1900 to 1998 and include the various Year Books, Bulletins, News, and other regularly produced publications from the Hort. These are a rich source of information about Hort sponsored events and organizational matters, as well as information about Hort's primary subject focus: horticulture. The program calendars include more detailed information about sponsored lectures and educational programs. The ephemera includes a range of material concerning membership, Flower Shows, lectures and other events, pilgrimages/tours, and other subjects. Among the miscellaneous items are the constitution, by-laws, some addresses, and monthly reports of the New York Horticultural Society (not to be confused with the Hort), the first such organization in America, founded in New York City in 1818 and active through the end of the nineteenth century.
  - Subseries VI.A. Hort Periodicals, 1900-1998; 9.08 Linear feet
    The subseries includes periodical publications issued over time by the Hort that, generally, had its membership as the principal audience. The content and titles of these changed somewhat over time, but generally included information about organizational matters, such as upcoming events, and horticulture-related short articles and book reviews. Following is a general summary of the content of the titles in the subseries:
    Memoirs: Three volumes that include the papers read at conferences organized by Hort in 1902, 1907, and 1926.
    Journal: This ran from April 1906 to July 1924. It Includes annual reports, proceedings of Hort meetings, reports on the various flower exhibitions, library accessions, committee reports, and papers/lectures on horticultural matters. It was replaced by the Year Book.
    Year Book: Started in May 1925, replacing the Journal. It includes annual reports, lectures/papers, flower show reports, accessions, etc. For the first few Year Books, the period covered is roughly August to May of the following year. In 1927, publication shifted to a calendar year basis. These appear to have ended in 1940, though a Year Book was published in 1951 to commemorate the events of 1950, the Hort's 50th anniversary year.
    Monthly Bulletin / Bulletin: The Bulletin appears to have started about January 1930. It started as a small pamphlet with short announcements concerning upcoming meetings and events/programs, new members, and accessions. By the early 1930s, it expanded to include lists of awards given for exhibits at the monthly meetings. By 1933, it further expanded to include transcripts or summaries of lectures. By 1934, a glossy version appeared, with increasing numbers of photographs. In Feb 1942, the Bulletin started presenting annual reports for the prior year, fully replacing the Year Book. The Monthly Bulletin ended in 1947, going to quarterly in 1948. It ceased publication with the first quarter 1950.
    News: It started in January 1951, replacing the Bulletin. Slimmed down from the Bulletin and much more casual, the News no longer included annual reports or articles, but focused on announcements, award winners, accessions, and basic membership information, though over time the content got more expansive. It was produced irregularly and ended in early 1957.
    Bulletin: Reintroducing the former title and replacing the News, the new Bulletin included both basic announcements and short articles, including book reviews. Starting in 1957, the Bulletin continued until 1973, though by 1970 it had been scaled down in size and scope. An announcement-oriented Member Newsletter started in late 1969, overlapping with the Bulletin through 1973. After 1973, the Member Newsletter (with the title shortened to just Newsletter in 1983) continued; the latest copy held by the subseries dates from 1998. The subseries holds a set of cards that represent an index to the Bulletin for the years 1958-1962.
    Garden was a bi-monthly publication of The Garden Society, a division of the NY Botanical Garden. Subscriptions to Garden were a benefit of membership in one of the institutions comprising The Garden Society, of which Hort was one. The bulk of the magazine content was common to all institutions, but some front pages were content specific to Hort. The content was horticulture-related and was not concerned with Hort organizational and event matters.The subseries holds issues from 1977-1984 and 1986.
    The subseries is arranged by periodical title, advancing in roughly chronological order.
    Items with the prefix "HSNY-" are freestanding, bound, multi-issue volumes. Items with the prefix "P-" are unbound single issue publications in small pamphlet boxes.
    - Memoirs, Vols I and II (bound), 1904, 1910 (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-1)
      Volume I is the Proceedings of the International Conference on Plant Breeding and Hybridization (30 September-2 October 1902). Volume 2 is the Proceedings of the International Conference on Plant Hardiness and Acclimatization (1-3 October 1907). Both conferences held at the American Institute of the City of New York and at the New York Botanical Garden.
    - Memoirs, Vol III (bound), 1927 (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-2)
      Vol III is Papers Presented at the International Conference on Flower and Fruit Sterility (12-14 August 1926).
    - Memoirs, Vol III (copy 2) (bound), 1927 (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-3)
    - 1st and 2nd Annual Reports, 1900-1902 (Offsite-box 102, Box P-1, Folder 1)
    - Journal of the Horticultural Society of New York (2 folders), 1906 April-1920 November (Offsite-box 102, Box P-1, Folder 2-3)
      Includes Vol. 1, numbers 1-18, missing 4; Vol. II, numbers 1-27. Vol. III, No. 12 (see below) includes an index to the first three volumes of the Journal. Vol. 1, No. 1 of April 1906 includes the 3rd, 4th and 5th Annual Reports.
    - Journal of the Horticultural Society of New York (2 folders), 1921 February-1924 July (Offsite-box 102, Box P-2, Folder 1-2)
      Includes Vol. III, Numbers 1-12, missing #9; Vol, IV, Number 1. Also includes a bound collection of Volumes II, III and IV of the Journal; this collection includes the Vol. III, No. 9 that is missing from the standalone issues. Vol. III, No. 12 includes an index to the first three volumes of the Journal.
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1924-27 (bound), 1924 August-1927 January (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-4)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1924-27 (copy 2) (bound), 1924 August-1927 January (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-5)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1927-29 (bound), 1927 January-1930 January (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-6)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1927-29 (copy 2) (bound), 1927 January-1930 January (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-7)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1930-34 (bound), 1930 January-1935 January (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-8)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1935-38 (bound), 1935 January-1939 January (Offsite-box 92, Volume HSNY-9)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1935-38 (copy 2) (bound), 1935 January-1939 January (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-10)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1939-41 (bound), 1939 January-1941 January (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-11)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York, 1939-41 (bound) (copy 2), 1939 January-1941 January (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-12)
    - Year Book of the Horticultural Society of New York (loose) (3 folders), 1930-1937, 1950 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 1-3)
      Includes original standalone copies of six Year Books, for years 1930, 1932, 1935, 1936, 1937, and 1950. There are four copies of the 1950 HSNY 50th anniversary year book (the cover of which is dated for its publication year of 1951).
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1930-32 (bound), 1930 January-1932 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-13)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1930-32 (copy 2) (bound) (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-14)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1930-31 (loose), 1930 April-1931 December (Offsite-box 102, Box P-3, Folder 1)
      Includes original standalone copies of some Bulletins for these years.
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1933-34 (bound), 1933 January-1934 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-15)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1933-34 (copy 2) (bound), 1933 January-1934 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-16)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1935-36 (bound), 1935 January-1936 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-17)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1935-36 (copy 2) (bound), 1935 January-1936 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-18)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1937-38 (bound), 1937 January-1938 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-19)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1937-38 (copy 2) (bound), 1937 January-1938 December (Offsite-box 93, Volume HSNY-20)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1939-40 (bound), 1939 January-1940 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-21)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1939-40 (copy 2) (bound), 1939 January-1940 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-22)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1941-42 (bound), 1941 January-1942 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-23)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1941-42 (copy 2) (bound), 1941 January-1942 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-24)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1943-44 (bound), 1943 January-1944 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-25)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1943-44 (copy 2) (bound), 1943 January-1944 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-26)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1945-46 (bound), 1945 January-1946 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-27)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1945-46 (copy 2) (bound), 1945 January-1946 December (Offsite-box 94, Volume HSNY-28)
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1947-48 (bound), 1947 January-1948 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-29)
      The Monthly Bulletin ceases at October 1947, replaced by a Bulletin produced quarterly beginning in 1948.
    - Monthly Bulletin, 1947-48 (copy 2) (bound), 1947 January-1948 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-30)
    - Monthly Bulletin (loose) (3 folders), 1934-1937 (Offsite-box 102, Box P-3, Folder 2-4)
      Includes incomplete sets of unbound Monthly Bulletins.
    - Monthly Bulletin (loose) (3 folders), 1938-1941, 1946 (Offsite-box 103, Box P-4, Folder 1-3)
    - Bulletin, 1949-50 (bound), 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-31)
      The final Bulletin was published for first quarter 1950.
    - Bulletin, 1949-50 (copy 2) (bound), 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-32)
    - News,1951-52 (bound), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-33)
    - News,1951-52 (copy 2) (bound), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-34)
    - News,1953-54 (bound), 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-35)
    - News,1953-54 (copy 2) (bound), 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-36)
    - News,1955-56 (bound), 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-37)
    - News,1955-56 (copy 2) (bound), 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-38)
    - News (loose), 1951-1957 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 4)
      Includes original standalone copies of some News for these years.
    - Bulletin, 1957-59 (bound), 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-39)
      The first number of 1957 is still called News. The title Bulletin returns in July 1957.
    - Bulletin, 1957-59 (copy 2) (bound), 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-40)
    - Bulletin, 1957-59 (loose) (2 folders), 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 103, Box P-5, Folder 1-2)
    - Bulletin, 1960-61 (bound), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-41)
    - Bulletin, 1960-61 (loose) (2 folders), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 103, Box P-5, Folder 3-4)
    - Bulletin, 1962-63 (bound) (Offsite-box 95, Volume HSNY-42)
    - Bulletin, 1962 (loose) (Offsite-box 103, Box P-5, Folder 5)
    - Index to Bulletin, 1958-1962 (Offsite-box 104, Box P-8, Cards -)
    - Bulletin, 1963-1966 (loose) (4 folders), 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 103, Box P-6, Folder 1-4)
    - News (loose), 1963 November-1965 March (Offsite-box 103, Box P-6, Folder 5)
      Includes reminders of events and other messages spun off into a separate document, formerly included in the Bulletin.
    - Bulletin, 1958-1961 (loose, additional copies) (3 folders) (Offsite-box 103, Box P-6, Folder 6-8)
    - Bulletin, 1962-1966 (loose, additional copies) (6 folders) (Offsite-box 104, Box P-7, Folder 1-6)
    - Bulletin, 1967-69 (bound), 1967-1969 January (Offsite-box 96, Volume HSNY-43)
    - Bulletin, 1967-69 (loose, 2 copies) (6 folders), 1967-1969 Summer (Offsite-box 85, Folder 4-9)